Birgit you make it do it makes it
比尔吉特，你做到了，做到了
alright good afternoon
下午好
hmm welcome to modules in one lesson my
嗯，欢迎来到我的一堂课中的模块
name is Mark Reynolds I work on Java
我叫Mark Reynolds我在Java上工作
many other things so this is a a skim on
许多其他事情，所以这是一个略读
the surface of of the module system and
模块系统的表面和
the modular platform in the modular
模块化平台中的模块化平台
modular JDK and all of that I am in
模块化JDK以及我所从事的所有工作
attempt to show you in in real time some
尝试实时向您展示一些
highlights what what does it mean to
强调什么意思
create a module how do you make one
创建一个模块如何制作一个
model depend upon another show you how
模型取决于另一个向您展示
deeply integrated the module system is
深度集成的模块系统是
into the platform and along the way show
进入平台并一路展示
you a few other things that maybe aren't
你可能还没有的其他一些东西
that tightly related to the module
与模块紧密相关
system but they're cool features in Java
系统，但它们是Java的很酷的功能
9 that I think I think a lot of people
9我认为我认为很多人
don't yet know about so I'll highlight
尚不知道，所以我将重点介绍
those as well and hopefully at the end
那些以及希望最后
we'll have some time for questions so
我们将有一些时间来提问
let's get going with our one lesson here
让我们在这里上一堂课
so I'm here in in a shell and you know
所以我在一个外壳里，你知道
what one of the one of the curses of
的诅咒之一
working on the jdk itself is you pretty
在jdk本身上工作很漂亮
much have to live on the command line
必须住在命令行上
much of the time because when you're
很多时候，因为当你
working on the next version the platform
在平台的下一版本上工作
the old versions of the IDs don't yet
ID的旧版本还没有
support the new stuff that you're
支持您的新事物
working on maybe you're if you're just
如果你只是在工作
doing a new library yeah sure you might
做一个新图书馆，是的，你可能会
you you might be fine but when you're
你也许很好，但是当你
when you're doing deep surgery on the
当您在进行深层手术时
libraries in the virtual machine and
虚拟机中的库和
changing the language then you're toast
改变语言，那么你就敬酒
so it's it's back to the command line
这样就回到了命令行
for you and that's kind of where we live
为了你，这就是我们生活的地方
a lot of the time so I've got a good
很多时候，我有一个很好的
look I've got a nine volt here JDK 9
看起来我这里有9伏特JDK 9
build I can show you what the version is
建立，我可以告诉你什么版本
I built this just a couple of days ago
我是几天前建造的
so it's its latest version of the jigsaw
这是拼图的最新版本
Jake prototype for a while Jake was way
杰克原型有一段时间了
ahead of the actual JDK 9 code these
在实际的JDK 9代码之前，这些
days it's it's really pretty close it
天真的很近了
runs a little bit of head and then we
跑了一点头，然后我们
then we bake things and
然后我们烘烤东西，
and through a bunch of tests and then
通过一堆测试，然后
merge them in jdk 9 main line of course
将它们合并到jdk 9主线中
we're trying to be towards the end of
我们正在努力接近
the release so if those differences
发布，如果这些差异
really really small these days anyway
这些天真的很小
that's that's that's the version that
那就是那个版本
we're running and to start off just have
我们正在跑步，开始时只有
a really trivial application here it's
一个非常琐碎的应用程序
it's hello world whoa they see the
你好，世界，他们看到了
original but it's a bit but it's a
原始的，但有点，但这是一个
little bit different so it's a hello
有点不同，这是你好
world you know inspired by our brethren
您所知的世界受到我们弟兄们的启发
in the land of JavaScript we have a left
在JavaScript领域，我们还有一个
pad method here kind of does the obvious
垫方法在这里做得很明显
and and the main method takes takes it
并且主要方法需要它
takes some some input constructs a a
需要一些输入构造aa
hello world string and it left pads it
你好世界字符串，它留下了它
and prints it out so pretty simple let's
并打印出来非常简单，让我们
let's just do the normal old compilation
让我们做普通的旧编译
thing here you see if I remember how to
事情在这里，你看看我是否记得如何
how to do this what we got we got make a
如何做到这一点，我们得到了一个
random other stuff actually before we
实际上在我们之前随机其他东西
get to that I need to show you a couple
我需要给你看几个
of other things so one is J shell how
其他事情之一就是J shell如何
many people have heard of J shell how
很多人听说过J shell
many people have plight played with J
很多人和J打过交道
shell okay J shells cool try it out so J
shell好吧J shell很酷，请尝试一下，这样J
shell
贝壳
welcome to James shell what can you do
欢迎来到James Shell，您能做什么
in J shell well you can even you can
在J shell中，您甚至可以
type expressions it does math you know
输入表达式，它可以算出数学
big deal you can assign variables you
可以分配变量
can ask it to do
可以要求它做
tap completion on the variable axle it's
可变轴上的攻丝完成
an instance of the string class and it
字符串类的实例，它
goes off in the string class asked well
在字符串类中问得很好
what methods are here you can then do do
您可以在这里做什么方法
completion on methods here it tells me
这里的方法完成告诉我
that oh they're actually two overloads
哦，他们实际上是两个超载
one day there's one that takes a single
有一天，只有一天
argument another that takes two
争论需要两个
arguments press tab again to see
参数再按一次标签即可查看
documentation and what does it do it
文档及其用途
shows you a summary of the Javadoc
向您展示Javadoc的摘要
right there in the tool so X up sub
就在工具中，所以X向上子
string two comma say 1 comma 3 and we
字符串两个逗号说1逗号3，我们
get whoo so ok so that it
哇，好吧，让它
tiny tiny intro to Jay Chou so we got
周杰伦的微小介绍，所以我们得到了
the string variable X what else can we
字符串变量X我们还能做什么
ask about X we can ask what its classes
询问X我们可以询问它的类
we can ask its class
我们可以问它的班级
now what module is it in every class in
现在在每个课程中它是什么模块
the module system you have your class
您上课的模块系统
Madrid ek now is in a specific module
马德里ek现在在特定模块中
and this class draw blank string is in
此类绘制空白字符串在
the module called Java a base which
Java模块称为基础
contains the foundation of the system
包含系统的基础
the fundamental stuff and and that
基本的东西
module object we can ask what its
我们可以问模块对象
classes it's an instance of a brand-new
类是一个全新的实例
type a new new type in the java.lang
在java.lang中输入新的新类型
package called module which is the
包称为模块
reflective runtime view of what a module
反射模块的运行时视图
is so it really is wired pretty pretty
所以真的很漂亮
deeply in we can look at some other
深入我们可以看看其他
classes let's import Java dot sequel
类让我们导入Java点续集
into RJ shell environment and we'll make
进入RJ Shell环境，我们将
a timestamp say times 10 of 0 clip keys
时间戳说乘以0的10个剪辑键
mark J shell thankfully has history and
马克·J·谢尔（J Shell）幸运地拥有历史并
tab completion just like any any
标签补全
reasonable shell so we can ask what T's
合理的外壳，所以我们可以问什么T
classes and it's module
类及其模块
Javadoc sequel has its own module it's a
Javadoc续集有自己的模块
different thing if you just have have
如果只是有另一件事
the base module you won't have any of
您将没有的基本模块
the sequel types if you if you're
如果你是续集类型
writing a modular application and you
编写模块化应用程序，您
need to use sequel then you need to make
需要使用续集，那么你需要
sure that somewhere along the line the
确保沿线某处
module that contains your code requires
包含您的代码的模块要求
sequel and we'll see more about that
续集，我们将看到更多有关此的内容
later
后来
already so that's J shell what else oh
已经是J壳了，还有什么哦
right
对
so as I as I said this morning they're
就像我今天早上说的那样
there their lot there's lots of
他们那里很多
confusion I see about being a people
我对成为一个人感到困惑
thinking oh well Java 9 is not going to
想哦，Java 9不会
run old code I have to compare
运行我必须比较的旧代码
everything everything to modules or
一切都到模块或
there are lots of incompatibilities
有很多不兼容性
because they they're hiding internal cat
因为他们隐藏了内部猫
classes inside of modules and stuff like
模块内部的类和类似的东西
that so just to make a point here I have
只是为了在这里提出一点
here swing set to dart and in anybody
在这里秋千设置为飞镖，任何人
remembers the swing set demo back in the
记得在
old days when swing was a thing yeah so
过去，秋千是一件很重要的事情，所以
swing swing set to what you know it's
秋千设置为您所知道的
the mother of all swing them as it demos
所有人的母亲在演示时摇摆他们
every swing component in every possible
一切可能的每个挥杆部件
mode this is the exact jar file from JDK
模式，这是来自JDK的确切jar文件
5ga dated 2000 for the star file is a
日期文件的日期为2000年的5ga是
teenager Java not jsr yeah right swing
少年Java不是jsr是的右摇摆
set to jar Katie canine build model
设置为jar凯蒂犬建立模型
system everything and yes it it works
系统的一切，是的，它的工作原理
all that stuff is there we've got you
所有的东西都在那里，我们有你
know the spaceman the kids so all the
认识太空人的孩子，所以所有的
babies that were born when swing was
秋千出生时出生的婴儿
developed in the early days there like
在早期发展像
off in college now you know okay so
现在大学毕业了，你知道吗
there there is actually a lot of
实际上有很多
compatibility in nine it's not as bad as
九个方面的兼容性不如
you may have heard yes there are issues
您可能听说过，有问题
but their issues with every major
但是每个专业的问题
platform release because we have to be
平台发布，因为我们必须
able to move the platform forward
能够推动平台向前发展
alright so now let's go back to our our
好了，现在让我们回到我们的
hello thing so you've got this little
你好，所以你有这么一点
guy here named in Java let's compile it
用Java命名的家伙进行编译
Java CD classes
Java CD类
or source or go to I love I love tap
或来源或去我爱我爱水龙头
completion okay we do that jar it up in
完成，好吧，我们把它塞进去
the usual way let's put this in a Lib
通常的方法让我们把它放到库中
directory jar but I keep typing that it
目录jar，但我一直在输入
is some Freudian thing
是弗洛伊德的东西
openjdk and boom it works and we can
openjdk和繁荣它起作用，我们可以
type
类型
any arguments and it left pass the
任何参数，它都通过了
string okay big deal mark you just made
你刚刚做的字符串好吗？
a jar file this is like Java 101 why are
一个jar文件，就像Java 101一样，为什么
you wasting our time on this let's make
您在此浪费我们的时间，让我们
a little change we will convert this
稍作更改，我们将转换为
into a trivial module how do we do that
到一个简单的模块中，我们该怎么做
well first crank up my favorite IDE
首先，启动我最喜欢的IDE
namely Emacs here's here's here's that
即Emacs这里是这里
main class what we did so does main
主班我们这样做的主要
classes down in its in its package
在其包装中分类
directory or org slash open JDK slash
目录或组织斜杠打开JDK斜杠
hello we're going to put a new file
你好，我们要放一个新文件
called module info at the root doesn't
根本没有调用模块信息
go in any particular package directory
进入任何特定的软件包目录
so but module info files are new thing
所以模块信息文件是新事物
diseases these are where module
这些是模块的疾病
declarations go module declarations are
声明去模块声明是
part of the language there they're baked
他们烤的语言的一部分
in pretty deeply to make a module you
深入地制作一个模块
give it a name or open JDK hello this
给它起个名字或打开JDK
module doesn't need any other modules
模块不需要任何其他模块
actually it needs the baseball module
实际上它需要棒球模块
but since every module needs the base
但是由于每个模块都需要基础
module except for the base module we
除了基本模块，我们
actually don't need to say that you can
实际上不需要说你可以
if you want but it has no value so we'll
如果您想要，但它没有价值，那么我们将
just do that we've got a module info
只是这样做，我们有一个模块信息
this name is our module and now let's
这个名字是我们的模块，现在让我们
compile bad again
再次编译不好
unless classes okay cool we jar that up
除非课程还不错，否则我们把它搞砸了
whoops now what's in hello jar now we've
哎呀，现在你好在罐子里
got module enjoy class module inside out
得到了模块享受类模块由内而外
Java file is compiled by the compiler
Java文件由编译器编译
into module info class file you can job
到您可以工作的模块信息类文件中
it you can run it through Java P I'll
你可以通过Java P运行它
just use the classes directory here and
只需在这里使用classes目录并
it tells you well yeah that's set that's
它很好地告诉你，是的
what we expect that the requires base
我们期望的需求基础
was inserted to helpfully by the
是由
compiler this this hello jar you can
可以编译这个hello jar
actually you can actually run it as a on
实际上，您实际上可以将其作为
the class path and the module info file
类路径和模块信息文件
is ignored so just as I ran it on a
被忽略，所以就像我在
class path before I can do so again but
上课之前，我可以再做一次
I can also treat that Lib directory as a
我也可以将该Lib目录视为
new thing the module path module path is
模块路径模块路径是新事物
where you put actual modules in your jar
您将实际模块放在jar中的位置
files that have module infos in them
包含模块信息的文件
although they're they're details that
尽管它们是细节
I'll get it get and get into in my
我将得到它并进入我的
second talk tomorrow so Java module half
明天第二讲，所以Java模块一半
Lib I'm going to tell it what module I
Lib我要告诉它我使用哪个模块
want to run JDK hello and I need to tell
要运行JDK的问候，我需要告诉
it what class in that module to run and
它在该模块中运行什么类并
that is me now okay
我现在可以了
big deal but it but it is is sort of the
没什么大不了的，但是那有点
first baby step two we just took that
第一个婴儿第二步，我们只是采取了
some that simple hello world app and
一些简单的Hello World应用程序
it's now a module and and now we can get
现在是一个模块，现在我们可以
going and do some more interesting
去做一些更有趣的事情
things I love of other questions we can
我喜欢其他问题的事情
ask about it in its in its life as a
在其生命中询问它
module so we get we can ask we can ask
模块，以便我们可以询问我们可以询问
the runtime system okay look at the
运行时系统好吧，看看
module path and describe a module for me
模块路径并为我描述一个模块
and here it's printing out the runtimes
在这里打印出运行时
view of what that module is saying that
该模块在说什么
it requires Java dot base that was
它需要Java点基础
mandated by the language spec it
由语言规范授权
contains a package or dead open JDK
包含一个包或完全打开的JDK
hello and of course it's name is org
你好，当然是组织名称
open JDK dot hello let's see what else
打开JDK dot hello让我们看看还有什么
yeah okay so moving along just to make
是的，所以继续前进只是为了
to make life simpler I'm going to make
使生活更简单
an entry point and we've been had we've
切入点，我们一直在
enhanced the poor old jar tool quite a
增强了可怜的旧jar工具
bit in this release with all kinds of
此版本中的所有内容
convenient things such as making
制作等方便的事情
specifying entry points and in in the
指定入口点，并在
module system the entry point for a
模块系统的入口点
module is actually recorded in the
模块实际上记录在
module info dot class file and now to
模块信息点类文件，现在到
run that I don't need to specify the
运行我不需要指定的
class name anymore because there's now a
类名，因为现在有一个
main class associated with the module
与模块关联的主类
and if I ask it to describe that module
如果我要它描述那个模块
it will tell me well now I used to take
它会告诉我现在我以前服用
it should tell me what the main class is
它应该告诉我主要的课程是什么
there's a little bug okay what about no
那里有个小虫子
all right so we've got we've got this
好的，所以我们有这个
really simple module we've got a module
非常简单的模块，我们有一个模块
info we've got a main main Java
信息，我们有一个主要的主要Java
let's do refactoring refactoring is
让我们进行重构重构是
always fun right so we're going to
总是很有趣，所以我们要
refactor this into two modules right
重构成两个模块吧
since since you know again we know from
因为自从你再次认识我们
from from experience in the JavaScript
来自JavaScript的经验
world left town really needs to be its
世界左城真的需要成为它的
own module so we're input left pad in in
自己的模块，所以我们在输入左垫
its own module and have have the
它自己的模块，并具有
HelloWorld module depend on that module
HelloWorld模块取决于该模块
so we'll see how module dependences and
因此，我们将了解模块依赖性和
how how exports work so let's let's do
出口如何运作，让我们开始吧
some surgery first we've got to
首先要做一些手术
rearrange some of it some of this these
重新安排一些这些
directories here let's let's just arm
目录在这里，让我们来武装一下
classes we're going to rename source to
我们将要重命名源的类
org dot open JDK hello we're going to
org dot open JDK你好，我们要
make
使
a new source directory we're going to
我们要去的新的源目录
move org open data Colette okay hello
移动组织开放数据Colette好的，你好
into that and we're going to put some
进去，我们要放一些
some new stuff in there so in a modular
一些新的东西在那里，所以在模块化
source tree every module gets its own
每个模块都有自己的源代码树
directory inside of which you find a
您在其中找到目录
normal old package hierarchy so that
正常的旧程序包层次结构
module info Java is right under the
模块信息Java就在
directory whose name is the native the
名称是本机的目录
entire name of the module and yeah
模块的全名，是的
there's a bit of redundancy here because
这里有些冗余，因为
the name is a module was the same name
名称是模块，名称相同
as its principal in this case only
仅在这种情况下作为其主体
package but there you go it is the it is
包，但是你去那是它
the most sensible way to name to name
最明智的命名方式
modules you pick them pick the main
您选择的模块选择主要
package inside and that's the name of
里面的包，这就是
your modules please use reverse DNS it's
您的模块请使用反向DNS
just saner all right so let's ditch that
没事就好了，让我们放弃
okay so we've got this let's say ways
好的，所以我们要说的是
we're going to we're going to sorry
我们要去对不起
first let's let's refactor the main
首先，让我们重构主
method the main class rather we're going
方法主类，而我们要去
to take this out the left pad we're
把它拿出左垫我们
going to make a whole new module org dot
将要制作一个全新的模块组织点
open JDK dot txt or open JDK text let's
打开JDK点txt或打开JDK文本，让我们
say powder Java
说粉Java
yeah
是的
here we go package
这里我们包
I'm a class patter let's make this
我是一个班级模式让我们做这个
public good static keep life simple now
公益公益让生活变得简单
we need a module info for this text guy
我们需要这个文本家伙的模块信息
and that's going to go where's it going
这将继续下去
to go right here in the root of the
去这里的根源
module higher that this particular
高于此特定模块
modules package higher hierarchy so a
模块封装了更高的层次结构，因此
module gets a name whoops
模块获得一个名字
[Music]
[音乐]
there we go or OpenJDK texts now they're
我们去那里或现在的OpenJDK文本
there they're high-level there are three
他们是高级的，那里有三个
fundamental things about a module module
有关模块的基本知识
has a name it has some number of
有个名字
exported packages
出口包装
maybe zero and it has some other modules
可能为零，它还有一些其他模块
upon which it depends maybe just our
这取决于我们
Java top base which is what you get by
Java的基础知识
default so the text module is going to
默认，所以文本模块将
is creating an API for use by other
正在创建供其他人使用的API
modules so it needs to export its
模块，因此需要导出其
principal package so we write exports or
主体包，所以我们写出口或
got open JDK not text it only needs to
打开JDK不发短信，只需要
have it up base so we don't need to say
有基础，所以我们不必说
that here
在这里
and now we ought to be able to compile
现在我们应该能够编译
the text module let me make sure right
文本模块让我确定正确
to do or create it
做或创建它
I'll just cheat here
我只是在这里作弊
right let's draw that up there's no main
正确，让我们得出结论，没有主要的
class here oh oh dear
在这里上课哦哦亲爱的
I know makes a directory first jar sure
我知道先确定目录
we'll use that for you
我们将为您使用
okay so client we've got the classes
好的，所以客户我们已经上课了
we've got the classes we got the Lib
我们有课程，有自由图书馆
here's text jar Scott that got its
这是斯科特的文本罐
module info now we can't run that
模块信息，现在我们无法运行
because there's no cuz there's no no
因为没有，因为没有
main but now we can compile the Hello
main，但是现在我们可以编译Hello了
module which we first have to edit so
我们首先必须编辑的模块
remember fundamental things about a
记住关于
module it has a name it has exports and
模块，它的名字有出口，
it has to say what it requires and now
它必须说出它需要什么，现在
the Hello module is going to require or
Hello模块将需要或
open JDK text not not the package but
打开JDK文本不是包，而是
the module which happens to have that
恰好具有
pad that package of the same name
垫上同名包裹
alright let's compile that
好吧，让我们编译一下
now let's save our work first mark
现在让我们保存工作的第一标记
module not found or Gobind gatk text I
找不到模块或Gobind gatk文本I
didn't tell the compiler where to find
没有告诉编译器在哪里找到
the text module that we already compiled
我们已经编译的文本模块
so let's tell the compiler that the
所以让我们告诉编译器
compiler takes a module path just like
编译器采用模块路径，就像
the runtime takes a module path I cannot
运行时采用了我无法使用的模块路径
find symbol oh yeah that's 10 today - I
找到符号哦，是的，今天10点-我
love static typing pattern left pad
爱静态打字图案左垫
I love static typing really I do import
我喜欢静态输入，真的可以导入
or openjdk text patter okay what do we
或openjdk文本模式好吗，我们该怎么办
got inner Lib directory but not free
有内部Lib目录，但不是免费的
have to make the jar market
必须做罐子市场
Lib directory to jar files we can now
将目录解放到jar文件，我们现在可以
run
跑
oh I forgot that mean let me just do
哦，我忘了那意味着我就去做
this
这个
hello world and now it's actually
你好世界，现在实际上
assembling at runtime it gets that it
在运行时组装它
gets the text module instantiates that
获取文本模块实例化
it gets
它得到
hello module in centuries that hooks
几个世纪以来的hello模块
them up and it's running in modular form
他们起来，并以模块化的形式运行
so fidelity is is really important
所以保真真的很重要
fidelity across phases we've tried as
我们尝试过的各个阶段的保真度
much as possible to make I mean not just
尽可能使我的意思不仅仅是
mundane things like the command line
命令行之类的世俗事物
options although it's the ability there
选项，虽然这是那里的能力
is useful too but the model system works
也是有用的，但是模型系统可以工作
as much as possible the same way at
尽可能以相同的方式
compile time as it does at runtime so
像在运行时一样编译时间，因此
errors are detected in the same way more
以相同的方式检测错误
or less in both phases and the error
两个阶段或更少且错误
messages are very similar so for example
消息非常相似，例如
in the Lib directory suppose I remove
在Lib目录中，假设我删除了
Lib texts are well we actually actually
Lib文本很好，我们实际上
already saw an example of this but I'll
已经看到了一个例子，但我会
just run through it again but if I try
只需再次运行它，但如果我尝试
to compile the Hello module even though
即使编译Hello模块
I did have given it the module path it
我确实给了它模块路径
says module not found or go for JDK text
表示找不到模块或输入JDK文本
because that jar file just isn't there
因为那个jar文件不存在
if I try to run the hello module I get a
如果我尝试运行hello模块，我会得到一个
similar message module open JDK text not
类似的消息模块打开的JDK文本不行
found it's not in the Lib directory so
发现它不在Lib目录中，所以
you know that this is one of it one of
你知道这是其中之一
the great things about reliable
关于可靠的伟大之处
configuration it's not is reported right
配置它不是正确的报告
away if something is missing it's not
如果缺少某些东西，那不是
like it's not like the class path where
就像它不像类路径一样
if something is missing you don't
如果缺少什么，你就不会
discover it until your applications been
发现它，直到您的应用程序被
up and running for hours or days you
启动并运行数小时或数天
know right away when something is
知道什么时候马上知道
missing okay let's just recompile
缺少，让我们重新编译
texts model we'll get that back back
文本模型，我们会把它找回来
into place let's go into our requires so
进入我们的需求
here's the measures of the module into a
这是该模块的措施
four for the hello module what if what
四个用于hello模块
happens is we comment out this requires
发生是因为我们对此进行了注释
can we compile it what do you think now
我们可以编译一下吗，您现在怎么想
that's weird
这很奇怪
Oh nuggets of two livability
哦，两个宜居的掘金
it was confused by the classes directory
它被classes目录弄糊涂了
yep there we go package org open JDK
是的，我们去包org open JDK
text does not exist because we didn't
文字不存在，因为我们没有
require the right thing so the compiler
需要正确的东西，所以编译器
knows all about that too it's recompile
也知道这一切，它可以重新编译
mmm
嗯
okay there is their variety variety of
好吧，有各种各样的
other errors and another interesting one
其他错误和另一个有趣的错误
is if you fail to export something so
如果您无法导出某些内容
this is exported API I could comment
这是导出的API，我可以评论
this out recompile the compiler would
这样重新编译编译器会
catch it I could try to run it at run
抓住它我可以尝试在运行时运行它
time and the run time system would
时间和运行时间系统将
capture it as well alright so enough of
很好地捕获它
enough of that little little demo so the
足够的小演示，所以
JDK is we've decomposed we've used this
JDK是我们已经分解了，我们使用了这个
module system to decompose it into a set
模块系统将其分解为一组
of modules you can if you just type Java
您只需键入Java就可以设置模块数量
dot list modules you'll get the entire
点列表模块，您将获得整个
list there are quite a lot of them ooh
清单上有很多哦
let's page that many of them they start
让我们分页，他们开始了很多
with the letters JAV a dot because
用字母JAV点，因为
they're part of a Java SE platform so
它们是Java SE平台的一部分，因此
they're you know they're official there
他们是你知道他们在那里的官方
blessed by the by the JCP and all that
受到JCP和所有这些的祝福
other all that other good stuff there
其他所有其他好东西
are a bunch of other modules they start
是他们开始的一堆其他模块
with jdk dot because they're part of
带有jdk点，因为它们属于
their jdk specific some of them are
他们的JDK特有的一些是
internal they don't export any api is
内部他们不导出任何API是
outside of the jdk some of them are
在jdk之外，其中一些是
parts of the jdk that you could actually
您实际上可以在JDK的某些部分
write code against they have AP eyes
针对他们的AP眼睛写代码
that are say that our supported ins in
就是说我们在
some sense but they're they're not part
从某种意义上讲，但他们是他们不属于
of the standard so if you get a jdk from
标准的，所以如果你从
from some from somewhere else that might
来自其他地方的人
not have it there are quite a few
没有它有很多
modules 7575 modules only only 28 28 of
模块7575模块仅28 28
them are are so are so-called standard
它们是所谓的标准
models and they're all on a graph right
模型，它们都在图表上
wait you've got modules with dependence
等你有依赖模块
relationships you can make a graph and
关系，你可以做一个图和
here's the graph so quick quick tour
这是图，因此快速浏览
we've got java java base at the bottom
我们在底部有java java base
there if you look at this kind of the
在那里，如果你看着这种
bottom part of the slide many of these
幻灯片的底部
things are you know you can you can use
事情是你知道的，你可以使用
stuff down here without using stuff up
这里的东西不用用完
top right there is there's a module
右上方有一个模块
called Java SE which gets you all of the
称为Java SE，可以让您
api's that are part of java SE and not
属于Java SE而非api的api
part of java ee there's a module way at
java ee的一部分，有一种模块方式
the
的
called Java scee which includes the
称为Java scee，其中包括
union so if you really want everything
工会，所以如果你真的想要一切
that was in Java eight included
在Java中包括八
including all the EE stuff then you need
包括所有您需要的EE东西
to use to use that module otherwise Java
用于使用该模块，否则使用Java
SC is a somewhat trimmed-down set so
SC是稍微精简的设置，因此
base is down here it's got troubling
基地在这里，这令人不安
object draw blank string IO slang util
对象绘制空白字符串IO lang语util
net yeah but a bunch of security stuff
是的，但是有很多安全方面的东西
and they're all these other modules
这些都是其他模块
sitting on top and then all the JDK
坐在顶部，然后是所有JDK
models many of the JDK modules per
每个模型都模拟许多JDK模块
contain service providers that they gave
包含他们给的服务提供商
to get hooked up to the Java the Java
迷上了Java
modules through the service mechanism so
通过服务机制的模块
looking at this graph what do you notice
看这张图，你注意到了什么
about it anything
关于这件事
remember graph theory 101 sorry it's a
记住图论101对不起
dag there are no cycles right so this
dag没有正确的周期，所以这
module system doesn't allow cycles
模块系统不允许循环
that's a little bit of a controversial
这有点争议
decision but it doesn't allow cycles
决定，但不允许循环
because cycles in module graphs are
因为模块图中的周期是
generally a really bad practice and it's
通常是一个非常糟糕的做法，这是
not just my personal opinion experts in
不只是我的个人意见专家
the field have been advocating this for
该领域一直为此提倡
for quite a while so yeah no snow cycles
好一阵子了，没雪
yet there are ways to induce cycles at
但是有一些方法可以在
runtime if you really need to through
如果确实需要运行时
the reflection API but by default cycles
反射API，但默认为循环
are are just not a thing another cool
只是不是一件很酷的事情
thing and is they getting a little
事情，他们得到一点点
little teeny bit off-track again but I'd
小蝇头再次偏离轨道，但我会
love to show it a Java doc knows about
很乐意向您展示Java文档所了解的知识
modules now so the main Java doc page is
现在可以使用模块，因此Java文档主页面是
no longer a near infinite list of
不再是近乎无限的
packages it's actually a structured as a
打包它实际上是一个结构化的
list of modules you know there's there's
您知道的模块清单
Java Donbass but you can scroll down and
Java Donbass，但您可以向下滚动并
you see all of the Java ones first and
您会首先看到所有Java语言，
then eventually some JDK ones that have
然后最终有一些JDK
supported api's show up and and one of
支持的api的显示，并且其中之一
the cool things about this about the
关于这个很酷的事情
Java doc enhancements is you can go into
Java文档增强功能可以进入
a module and the main page for a module
一个模块和模块的主页
contains a partial module graph so it
包含部分模块图，所以它
shows you right there visually if you
如果您可以直观地看到您
use CORBA
使用CORBA
then you're also going to get RMI you're
那么你也将获得RMI
also going to get desktop because CORBA
也将获得桌面，因为CORBA
and desktop polls and data transfer and
和桌面民意测验以及数据传输以及
XML and of course everything ultimately
XML，当然还有一切
depends on Java based somehow so these
取决于基于Java的方式，所以这些
little graphs are really handy in the
小图真的很方便
Java Java doc to let you get a sense of
Java Java文档让您对
what's going on another really you know
发生了什么事真的你知道
quick ad for ultra cool feature in Java
Java中超酷功能的快速广告
doc Java doc has built-in search now
doc Java doc现已内置搜索
Java Script is good for something so if
Java脚本对某些事情很有用，所以如果
I want to see like job what does the job
我想看到像工作一样的工作
Lang model API look like I just typed
Lang模型API看起来像我刚刚输入的
that and boom I'm there you don't have
那和繁荣我在那里你没有
to go groveling through trees and
穿过树木丛生，
clicking left right and everywhere you
单击左右，到处都是
can just search and there you go so
可以搜索，然后就可以了
that's pretty slick
那很漂亮
okay so there we go one last thing I'd
好吧，我们要做的最后一件事
like to show you is is linking so in
希望表明您正在链接，所以在
Java 9 as part of jigsaw we've added a
Java 9作为拼图的一部分，我们添加了一个
thing that that Java has never had and
Java从未拥有过的东西
that is a linker you know CCC's always
您知道CCC始终是一个链接器
had linkers right why didn't Java have a
有正确的链接器，为什么Java没有
linker well because Java is
链接器很好，因为Java是
predominantly is a very dynamic language
主要是一种非常动态的语言
in terms of its runtime behavior the
就其运行时行为而言
module system imposes it just is
模块系统强加它就是
designed to impose just enough static
旨在施加足够的静态
constraints that we can do linking is
我们可以进行链接的约束是
one route this is one reason why it's
一条路线，这就是为什么
not you know it's not completely totally
你不知道那不是完全
lazy at least not by default so linking
懒惰至少不是默认情况下，所以链接
let lets us deliver the jdk as a bunch
让我们将jdk作为一堆交付
of module artifacts and you can link
模块工件的集合，您可以链接
custom images that contain just the
包含仅
modules that you need and you know very
您需要并且非常了解的模块
perhaps together with your own code so
也许与您自己的代码一起
here's this is a JDK I've been using
这是我一直在使用的JDK
it's got you know I've been directory in
你知道我已经在
a lib directory and legal and other
一个lib目录和法律和其他
stuff there's no arc our keys are in
东西没有弧线
there by the way the j-mods directory
在那里的j-mods目录
contains a bunch of J mod files and
包含一堆J mod文件和
there's one of these files for each each
每个文件都有一个
Java or JDK module in the system so
系统中的Java或JDK模块
there's 75 of these guys so J mod is a
这些人有75个，所以J mod是
for is their not jar files J mod is a
因为不是他们的jar文件，J mod是
different format it's specific to the
特定于
JDK it's sort of jar files on steroids
JDK是类固醇上的jar文件
because for the JDK itself we have to be
因为对于JDK本身，我们必须
able to handle you know things like
能够处理你知道的事情
native code and legal notices and in
本机代码和法律声明以及
configuration files and lots of other
配置文件和许多其他
stuff and you just can't there's no way
东西，你就是不可能
to take an ordinary jar file and match
拿一个普通的jar文件进行匹配
that in in a way that it actually makes
以某种方式
sense so J mods they write they are
因此，J mods写道
based on the zip format like jar but
基于像jar这样的zip格式，但是
their data case-specific at least for
至少针对其数据案例
now maybe they'll get standardized later
现在也许他们以后会标准化
if if there's a reason to do that later
如果以后有理由再做
on anyway given given that directory
在给定的目录下
full of J mod files you can run this new
完整的J mod文件，您可以运行此新文件
tool called J link I'll be obviously
称为J link的工具
enough you give it a module path
只要给它一个模块路径
you tell it what what modules you want
你告诉它你想要什么模块
you always have to tell jailing jailing
你总是必须告诉jailing
where to start
从哪儿开始
we're just to start which you can just
我们只是开始，您可以
make a simple image that has only the
制作一个只有
base module in it and we'll put that in
基本模块放入其中，我们将其放入
let's say JRE yeah that should work all
假设JRE是的，应该可以正常工作
right
对
it goes off in things for a while and
它会暂时消失
now we have our own custom JRE
现在我们有自己的自定义JRE
here's the size of the entire JDK 9
这是整个JDK 9的大小
build I've been working with 553
我一直在与553合作
megabytes here's the size of the JRE
这是JRE的兆字节
that I just made it's only 48 megabytes
我刚做的只有48兆字节
it's got a bin directory but it doesn't
它有一个bin目录，但是没有
have much in Java and well keytool
有很多Java和很好的keytool
because that part of the security stuff
因为那部分安全性
is in the base modules I can run this I
在基本模块中，我可以运行它
can list the modules in it
可以列出其中的模块
woohoo all it has is the base module ok
woohoo它所拥有的只是基本模块
we can go we can go further than this we
我们可以走，我们可以走得更远
can let's go let's run Lib let's run our
可以走吧，让我们运行Lib，让我们运行
hello module
你好模块
that son
那个儿子
well anyway that should work but it's
无论如何都应该正常工作，但这是
not working and I'm not going to be like
不工作，我不会像
getting real-time alright so we've got
得到实时的好，所以我们有
these two these two Jerry's I another
这两个这两个杰里是我另一个
cool thing Jalen can do is it can
Jalen可以做的很酷的事情是可以
compress so if you care more about space
压缩，如果您更关心空间
than you care about time there are
比你在乎时间
additional options we can use let's say
我们可以使用的其他选项
compress compression - is the highest
压缩压缩-最高
we're going to use a minimal VM and
我们将使用最小的VM
we're going to strip debug symbols what
我们将去除调试符号
am i doing
我在做什么
and we better put that somewhere else
我们最好把它放在其他地方
because that will conflict so this is
因为那会冲突，所以这是
going to do some compression it'll
要进行一些压缩，它将
strips strip things it'll use a
剥离东西，它将使用
stripped-down virtual machine that
精简的虚拟机
doesn't have things like JB MTI in it so
没有像JB MTI这样的东西
you can't monitor it remotely but maybe
您不能远程监控它，但也许
we're going to stick this on a small
我们将把它放在一个小的
device and that doesn't matter so it
设备，没关系，所以它
just goes off and it does some work to
刚熄灭，它做了一些工作
them to them to them to them and our
他们对他们对他们对我们
compressor area is only 15 mix but it'll
压缩机面积只有15混合，但会
run this it's Gaga drop a bass in it the
运行它，它是Gaga放低音的
whole deal
整个交易
and there you are okay so that's the
那里你还好，所以
demo so far we've got about 15 minutes
到目前为止，我们已经演示了15分钟
left for questions so if people would
离开了问题，所以人们是否会
like to ask questions that's great
喜欢问很棒的问题
there's there's lots of information
有很多信息
available there are the jigsaw is this
那里有拼图吗？
enormous project has been going on for
庞大的项目正在进行中
quite a few years it's got one two three
好几年了，一二三
four five six steps in in open JDK and
在开放的JDK中执行四五六步
entire jsr in the Java community process
Java社区流程中的整个jsr
if you go to open JDK java.net slash
如果您打开JDK java.net斜杠
project slash jigsaw you can find pretty
你可以找到漂亮的项目斜线拼图
much all the information that we have on
我们拥有的所有信息
it this URL is out of date sorry it
这个URL过期了对不起
should it should just say JDK java.net
它应该只说JDK java.net吗
JDK non Java deny will it will redirect
JDK non Java拒绝它将重定向
to the right place we we probably
在正确的地方，我们可能
publish the JDK 9 early access build
发布JDK 9早期访问版本
every week we publish the jigsaw early
每周我们都会尽早发布拼图游戏
access build every build so it's you
访问每个版本的构建，就是您
know whenever there is a whenever there
知道什么时候都有
are changes in the jigsaw specific
是拼图中的变化
forest those builds show up release date
森林那些建筑显示发布日期
well the scheduled occurrence schedule
计划好的发生时间表
says July 27th but with the drama
说7月27日，但随着戏剧
earlier this week I would say that
本周初我会说
release date is in doubt I have I don't
发布日期不确定我有没有
know when the release will be hopefully
知道什么时候会发布
it will be fairly soon
会很快
don't believe a word I have said I work
不相信我说过的话
for Oracle
对于Oracle
questions please is there a hand mic
问题，请问那里有麦克风吗
around or great or if you shot if you're
周围或很棒，或者如果您射击，
shy feel free to tweet me am reinhold
害羞，随时发推文给我
that'll work too hello over here yes -
那会在这里打招呼是的-
is there an equivalent to the class
有相当于班级的人吗
loader functionality for modules for
模块的加载程序功能
like dynamically generating classes in a
就像在
modular or something like that
模块化或类似的东西
is there equivalent to the class loader
有没有相当于类加载器
function I'm not sure so so so the
功能我不确定，所以所以
module system actually cares very little
模块系统实际上很少在乎
about class loaders and that that's
关于类加载器，那是
intentional as I camp as in order to
有意为我扎营
achieve good compatibility there are
实现良好的兼容性
lots of applications out there but do
那里有很多应用程序但是
lots of crazy things with class loaders
类加载器有很多疯狂的事情
and we want them to be able to leverage
我们希望他们能够利用
the module system you know as well as
您知道的模块系统以及
just the platform itself so is your
只是平台本身，您的平台也是如此
question can you can you create a module
问题你可以创建一个模块吗
ok can you load a module dynamically
好的，您可以动态加载模块吗
after the system has started up well do
系统启动好之后
anything dynamic currently I can see
我现在能看到的任何动态
that like even module contains a static
甚至模块都包含静态
set of classes and obviously things work
一组类，显然一切正常
but is run to download those classes at
但是可以在以下位置下载这些类
runtime from somewhere or you know
从某个地方运行时，或者您知道
designed I mean any no there so there
设计的意思是那里没有
there's definitely provision for dynamic
肯定有动态的规定
behavior it's not as dynamic as OSGi and
行为不像OSGi和
that it's not a sort of sea of modules
那不是各种各样的模块
that can come and go at any time in a
在任何时候都可以来来去去
completely dynamic way instead in order
完全动态的方式来代替
to get at to get a handle on the
去了解
dynamism so that we can do things like
动态性，以便我们可以做类似的事情
linking and also report errors earlier
链接并更早报告错误
in time rather than later there's a
及时而不是稍后
concept of layers so modules can be
层的概念，因此模块可以
essentially stacked in groups called
本质上是成堆的
layers of Lea one layer it layers are
一层Lea一层
hierarchical so layers layers can also
分层的，所以图层也可以
be in the directed acyclic graph if you
如果您在有向无环图中
just start up a system by default you
只需默认启动一个系统
get the boot layer that's where all the
获取所有的启动层
application models from the module taps
来自模块水龙头的应用模型
will be loaded and that's where all the
将被加载，这就是所有
platform modules are loaded but if
平台模块已加载，但如果
you're if you're doing something
你在做某事
advanced you're creating you have an
您正在创建的高级文件
application that they say has a plug-in
他们说有插件的应用程序
API and you and
API和您以及
user modules as as plugins to your
用户模块作为您的插件
framework or something then you can spin
框架或东西，然后你可以旋转
up a layer to load plug-in modules it'll
上一层来加载插件模块
be no sub-graphs of plug-in modules that
不能是插件模块的子图
relate to the model graph that's in the
与其中的模型图有关
lower layers so there's there's
较低的层，所以有
mechanism for all of that and that's you
所有这些的机制，就是你
know that's intended to handle the
知道这是为了处理
dynamic cases thank you where are we on
动态案例谢谢您我们在哪里
things like versioning I'm sorry hold up
诸如版本控制之类的事情，我很抱歉
closer where are we on things like
靠近我们在什么地方
versioning so you know obviously not
版本控制，所以您显然不知道
like last patent hell at the moment is
就像目前的最后一个专利地狱是
different differing versions you know
您知道的不同版本
I'm sure none of us here change our
我敢肯定，我们所有人都不会改变我们的
public api's but once in a while that
公共api，但偶尔
seems to happen right so I need to stand
似乎是对的，所以我需要站起来
here so I can hear you so where are we
在这里，我可以听到你的声音，我们在哪里
on versioning yes or you know so you
关于版本控制是还是您知道所以
know I wanna patch ecommons with version
知道我想用版本打补丁
1.2 that's 1.4
1.2就是1.4
right so so as I said this morning
对，所以我今天早上说
they're jigsaw does not attempt to solve
他们是拼图游戏，不会尝试解决
the multiple version problem which is is
多个版本的问题是
a really hard problem there number of
有一个非常困难的问题
reasons for that
原因
you know high-level summary if we did
你知道高级摘要，如果我们做了
you probably wouldn't like it at least
你可能至少不会喜欢
not with the tools that are available
没有可用的工具
now all of the tools that we have are
现在我们拥有的所有工具都是
tightly oriented towards you really
紧紧地面向你
trying to get only one version of
试图只获得一个版本
anything on the classpath right it's
在classpath上的任何东西都是
going to take fundamental changes to
将对
maven and other the other build tools to
Maven和其他构建工具
move beyond that so that they actually
超越这一点，以便他们实际上
convey more of the model graph they
传达更多的模型图
actually compute and allow those allow
实际计算并允许那些允许
multiple versions we also chose not to
多个版本，我们也选择不
put versions into the model system at
将版本放入模型系统中
this time because it's really critical
这次是因为这很关键
for adoptions to be able for people to
使人们能够收养
be able to use the tools that they're
能够使用他们所使用的工具
familiar with and guess what maven
熟悉并猜测什么行家
Gradle IV you every tool that deals with
Gradle IV为您处理的所有工具
jar files today has some way of doing
今天的jar文件有一些处理方法
version selection some way of doing
版本选择一些方法
conflicts they're all different the
冲突，他们都是不同的
heuristics they use to resolve conflicts
他们用来解决冲突的启发式方法
are all different if we actually had a
如果我们实际上有一个
version based resolver in jigsaw it
拼图中基于版本的解析器
would you know it would piss off some
你知道会生气吗
large group of people because it would
一大群人，因为它会
be different than at least one
与至少一个不同
maybe two of the major build tools and
也许是两个主要的构建工具，
and that would just be a huge barrier
那将是一个巨大的障碍
barrier to adoption so it has been a it
采用的障碍，所以一直是
has been a bit of a controversial
一直有争议
decision people think oh module system
决定人们认为哦模块系统
you must have versions and well no we
你必须有版本，好吧，我们
don't but we chose that in order to
不，但是我们选择它是为了
increase its approachability so that
增加其可及性，以便
people could use it sooner rather than
人们可以早点使用它，而不是
later eleven minutes left and sorry with
还剩十一分钟，对不起
the same reasoning of version and you
版本与您的推理相同
said you can specify a version in the
说您可以在
module right you cannot specify every
您无法指定每个模块的权利
minimum you can not specify the
至少您不能指定
reference all right so basically you can
引用好吧，所以基本上你可以
have just one version of a module you
您只有一个版本的模块
get you can have one version of a module
得到一个模块的一个版本
in any particular layer in any book so
在任何一本书的任何特定层中
if you're if you're in a more
如果你在另一个地方
sophisticated application and you really
复杂的应用程序，您真的
need to load different versions of
需要加载不同版本的
things you can spin up layers to do that
您可以旋转图层以完成此操作的事情
and the API is actually quite simple so
API实际上非常简单，所以
if you're doing doing a plug-in
如果您正在做插件
architecture you're writing you know
您正在编写的架构，您知道
something akin to an application server
类似于应用服务器的东西
you know doing fancy things with stuff
你知道用东西做花哨的事情
at runtime you can you can load
在运行时，您可以加载
different versions but we've but for now
不同的版本，但到目前为止
at least we've left out to the API not
至少我们没有考虑API
sure I'm not saying that we will get
当然我不是说我们会得到
there will never be versions in this
永远不会有版本
module system just that right now it
模块系统现在就可以了
didn't make sense from an adoption
通过收养没有意义
standpoint
立场
so our coefficient so you've put the
所以我们的系数，所以你把
module in the sort of is it like the
像这样的模块
source level of the code right and so if
代码的源代码级别正确，如果
someone goes and add something you have
有人去添加你拥有的东西
to go back and add something to the list
返回并添加一些东西到列表中
of modules that you're using let's say
假设您正在使用的模块数量
someone goes back roof access code and
有人回去屋顶访问代码，
takes something out is there any
拿出东西有没有
instrumentation that's being planned or
计划中的仪器或
you expect connecting a debugging that
您希望连接调试
says hey you've got this extra piece in
说嘿，你有这额外的一块
your modules you don't really need this
你的模块你真的不需要这个
you can get rid of it I keep a nice
你可以摆脱它，我保持很好
clean module systems I say yeah I I
我说的是清洁模块系统II
expect the unity the IDs and other
期望统一的ID和其他
tooling in in do in due course will
在适当的时候做工具
offer that level of advice all the
提供所有级别的建议
informations there right you can you can
那里的信息就可以
easily easily tell when when you're
轻松轻松告诉您何时
exporting a package that has no classes
导出没有类的包
in it for example you can you can
例如，在其中可以
identify when one module requires
识别何时需要一个模块
another but never actually uses like
另一个但从未真正使用过
statically any of the types in that
静态地
module so maybe that's the requires that
模块，所以也许这就是要求
you don't that you don't actually need
你不是你实际上不需要
so do you know just as we have tools
你知道我们拥有工具吗
that help clean up imports and stuff
帮助清理进口和东西
like that I you know all the foundation
这样，我知道所有基础
is there for tools to do quite a bit of
有工具可以做很多事情吗
analysis on modules
模块分析
this is against again this is related to
这再次与这有关
the versioning thing what did it make a
版本控制功能使它产生了什么
bit difficult for the CDC I process when
我处理CDC时有点困难
you don't have a versioning like I need
您没有像我需要的版本控制
to have a live version there on my Nexus
在我的Nexus上有一个实时版本
and then I need to do another module and
然后我需要做另一个模块
how would you handle this scenario it
您将如何处理这种情况
has to be packaged to do another module
必须打包以执行其他模块
I'm sorry the what process used an
对不起，什么程序使用了
acronym that I recognize now continuous
我认识的首字母缩写现在是连续的
integration or continuous they deployed
集成或连续部署
like one play continues integration it
就像一场戏继续融合一样
moves on with the snapshot version right
继续使用快照版本
environment perspective right Phase II
环境透视权第二期
maven or something so I found developing
Maven之类的东西，所以我发现发展
two different models one more use
两种不同的型号再使用
already live and I want to update that
已经直播了，我想更新一下
module and versioning is not supported
不支持模块和版本控制
right so how would you handle this
对，那么您将如何处理
scenario it's up to your build system in
场景取决于您的构建系统
your and your CI system to update the
您和您的CI系统来更新
model artifacts is needed just like they
就像它们一样需要模型工件
do today for jar files so I not sure I
今天要处理jar文件，所以我不确定
see a problem here but maybe I don't
在这里看到一个问题，但也许我没有
understand the question okay so module
了解问题好吗，所以模块
system ok I need to think about I'll
系统好，我需要考虑一下
come back the I to acute okay yes I'll
回到我那里，好吧，我会
be around catch me later
待会儿见
dum-dum-dum
哑巴
hello could you go back to the to the
你好，你可以回到
graph to the motorcross here we go
图到摩托车越野赛，我们去了
like for example I want to use Java SE
例如，例如，我想使用Java SE
OTE I can also exclude a module like
OTE我也可以排除类似的模块
Nova nope nope
Nova nope nope
SCE required requires core but if you
要求的SCE需要核心，但如果您
don't if you don't really don't want
如果你真的不想要的话就不要
CORBA course you want korvac on if you
如果您想在科瓦上学习CORBA课程
don't want corba then well just need
不想corba那么就只需要
don't require the SE EE module but do
不需要SE EE模块，但是需要
require Java SE and java xml WS and Java
需要Java SE和Java xml WS和Java
dot transaction and anything else but
点交易及其他
only CORBA was pulling in so here you
只有CORBA才加入，所以在这里您
can do that but we take it we take
可以做到，但我们接受
consistency really seriously if module a
如果模块a，一致性真的很重要
says it requires module B we're going to
说它需要模块B
go find a B and if we don't find a B
去找一个B，如果我们找不到一个B
that's an ER and what are the like the
那是一个ER，那是什么样的
color the color coding of the arrows the
为箭头颜色编码
color coding of the arrows is a blue
箭头的颜色编码为蓝色
arrow means there's an API dependence so
箭头表示存在API依赖关系，因此
the in the java dot sequel module it
在Java点续集模块中
exports packages that contain types and
导出包含类型和
the title end and those those types
标题结尾和那些类型
mention types in the java dot logging
在Java点记录中提及类型
module the grey arrows are are either a
模块中的灰色箭头是
pyramid a shinto pendants or it's an
金字塔神道吊坠，或者它是
arrow in the java dot base because
Java点基中的箭头，因为
everything depends on java dot base and
一切都取决于Java dot base和
would be boring to make all those arrows
制作所有那些箭头会很无聊
blue is you know is it is it the optimal
蓝色你知道这是最佳吗
design no probably not but so what's
设计可能不是，但是那是什么
there today
今天在那里
way down here wait wait for the mic
在这里，等待麦克风
please so that the recording makes sense
请使录音有意义
so if if you would export the module
因此，如果您要导出模块
that you don't export models use for
您不导出模型用于的
packages if you declare a module declare
包，如果您声明模块声明
module that has an interface and that's
具有接口的模块
everything that it declared declares so
它声明的一切都宣布如此
and so interfaces are low or a lower
因此界面较低或较低
level thing an interface or example we
级别事物接口或示例我们
just declare a patter interface you
只需声明一个模式接口
would not actually implement it would
不会实际实施
that be possible
可能的
oh yes yeah it in in in the in the
哦，是的，它在
little text module patter could have
小小的文本模块模式
been an interface there could be an
是一个接口，可能会有一个
internal class that's either say package
内部类，要么说包
private or maybe in another package
私人的或其他包装
that's not exported that provides the
没有导出的提供
implementation of patter patter patter
atter沥沥的实现
yet and and that patter interface could
而且，该模式界面可以
have a handy default method in it say
里面有一个方便的默认方法
that could go get that instance and
那可以去得到那个实例，
would you would it be a an idea to do it
你会做一个主意吗
as a separate module implementation
作为单独的模块实现
would that be oh yes you can totally
那会是哦，是的，你完全可以
separate interfaces and implementations
单独的接口和实现
you can have interface you can have a
你可以有界面，你可以有一个
module full of interfaces another module
充满接口的模块另一个模块
with implementations of those interfaces
这些接口的实现
but that all just works yep
但这一切都可以
it's aerobics it's good for you so how
有氧运动对您有好处，所以如何
would you recommend to move from javaee
您是否建议从javaee迁移
to jello 9 with with care and
小心地将jello 9和
deliberation just like any major release
像任何主要发行版一样进行审议
so so there we put in what put in lots
所以我们在那里放很多东西
of tools to help with this because we
工具来帮助解决这个问题，因为我们
know we know it's going to be a problem
知道我们知道这将是一个问题
1 1 1 fairly recent addition is there's
1 1 1最近添加的是
now a what what we've informally called
现在是我们非正式地称为
the big kill switch so we know that
大杀手开关，所以我们知道
there's a lot of code out there that
那里有很多代码
that accesses internal api's that are no
访问内部api的no
longer exported so so that's an illegal
出口时间更长，所以这是非法的
access there the flag is creatively
在那里访问标志是创造性的
called - - permit - illegal - access you
称为--许可证-非法-访问您
can you can run with that and and the
您可以与此同时运行吗？
module system is essentially turned off
模块系统基本上已关闭
but it's still there enough that it can
但它仍然在那里，它可以
report error messages so you can find
报告错误消息，以便您查找
out which bits of code are accessing
哪些代码正在访问
internals and we we've tried to make the
内部，我们试图使
error messages as descriptive as
错误消息的描述性
possible so you can go figure out oK
有可能，所以你可以找出来
you've got a class path full of you know
你有一个充满你知道的课程
dozens of jar files you got off central
您从中央下了几十个jar文件
you can now diagnose Excel you could you
您现在可以诊断Excel您可以
know which jar file has code into the
知道哪个jar文件中有代码
sass accessing which internal API and we
萨斯访问哪个内部API，我们
strongly encourage you go report a bug
强烈鼓励您报告错误
against that project and ask them to fix
针对该项目，并要求他们修复
it or if you have some time on your
还是如果您有一些时间
hands
手
submit a patch submit a pull request
提交补丁提交请求请求
whatever whatever whatever it is that
不管那是什么
they want so that that's that's one one
他们想要的就是那一个
useful tool for for migration one other
相互迁移的有用工具
question I had was I haven't thought
我有一个问题是我没有想到
this through so apologies victims names
通过这样的道歉，受害者的名字
me getting stoned at the end and with
我在最后被砸了
you you never dependent a good viewer
你你从不依赖一个好的观众
good yeah this so with the dependencies
好的，这与依赖项有关
are now sitting inside the module file
现在位于模块文件中
was there a discussion about getting
是否有关于获得的讨论
with the import statements oh why would
用导入语句哦，为什么
we get rid of them the important
我们摆脱了重要的
statement because import statements will
声明，因为导入声明将
tell you the dependency that your code
告诉您代码的依赖性
has
拥有
at the class level both then say that
然后在课堂上都说
you don't really need that because
你真的不需要那是因为
you're setting that at the package well
你在包装上设置好了
the library or packing level I think
我认为图书馆或包装水平
they're I think there's yes you could
他们是我认为你可以
you could and the compiler could in a
你可以和编译器可以在
sense infer what all the imports would
推断所有进口将
be based on the requires but I think
基于需求，但我认为
there's still value at the level of
仍然有一定价值
classes and interfaces to control what's
类和接口来控制什么
coming in just to keep your life saying
进来只是为了让你的生活说
especially if there are things like you
特别是如果有像你这样的事情
know to like class names that are
知道喜欢类名是
duplicated you wanna have some amount of
复制你想有一些
control over that and the two-legged the
对此和两足动物的控制
tooling supports them as as supported
工具支持他们如支持
import statements for years IDs filled
填写年份ID的进口对帐单
fill things in for you automatically and
自动为您填写内容，
it's it's not that not that much of a
不是因为不是那么多
burden just to the make sure that in
只是为了确保
this lineage right you export the
这个血统对你出口
package from the model from the
来自模型的包
application of the model that means that
该模型的应用意味着
you from the model that depends on that
您来自依赖于该模型的模型
model see only the interfaces exactly
模型仅查看接口
that at the cleric and that right it's
在神职人员那是正确的
right right if if module a requires
如果模块a需要则对
module B &amp; B has a package in it then
模块B和B中有一个包装
coded modulation only use the classes
编码调制仅使用类别
and interfaces in that packages B
和该软件包中的接口B
exports that package if B does not
如果B不导出该包
export that package suppose you have the
导出该包，假设您拥有
interface that you have internal and you
内部和内部的接口
don't export that long it means that you
不要出口那么长，这意味着你
use that internally yes if you in
在内部使用，如果您在
command that one and that but it's not
命令那个，那不是
visible
可见
absolutely well necessary okay careful
绝对必要，好吧，小心
it's not only is it not visible it's not
这不仅是不可见的，不是
accessible which is a much deeper
可访问性更深
guarantee the visibility is very weak
保证可见度很弱
guarantee communing the same old info
保证传达相同的旧信息
declare Asian declare several models no
申报亚洲申报几种型号否
no no various so it's a module
不，没有各种各样，所以这是一个模块
declaration declares only one mom
宣言只宣布一个妈妈
different exports you in this end oh
为此出口不同哦
yeah yeah well yeah you can export many
是的，你可以出口很多
packages you can require many other
您可能需要许多其他包装
modules
模组
there's also provision in the language
语言中也有规定
for services but that's a more advanced
服务，但这是更高级的
topic but yeah there you can serve you
主题，但是是的，您可以为您服务
certainly do those kinds of things all
当然可以做所有这些事情
right time is up thank you very much
正确的时间到了，非常感谢
I'll be around just later if you have
如果有的话我待会儿待会儿
questions
问题
you
您